Health insurance will prove to be your best companion in difficult times like accidental death and permanent disability. With the
COVID-19 pandemic continuing to spread among people, the
number and scale of health-related challenges are
bound to increase. We're not
only concerned about the virus itself, but we
also need to be mindful of
what to do if we fall ill.
One thing is absolutely clear: old
methods are no longer useful. We need to prepare ourselves for the new
normal. We need to
adopt safety measures and obtain health insurance
that suits your needs. If
you take good
care of yourself and stay fit and healthy, you
might wonder why you
need health insurance. COVID-19 is
n't the only thing we should
protect ourselves from. Even if you're perfectly healthy, there are
some things
that will make you pause and
consider purchasing adequate health insurance.
Friends, in today's video,
we'll talk
about a very good health insurance plan from ICICI Lombard
and understand how this health
insurance can be beneficial for you.
ICICI Lombard has
introduced Safeguard Insurance Co. Health Insurance with its prepaid card. This insurance
plan is for prepaid card retail members. According to this,
if the prepaid card
holder meets with an accident and has to be
hospitalized for treatment,
he/she will be covered. This is a Bytrify
health insurance plan
designed for prepaid customers. ICICI Lombard's
insurance plan will be available
at outlets spread across the country.
Members can avail insurance cover by making a free payment while shopping. The
insurance plan includes hospital treatment, free cash
benefit, death benefit, special background
image related hospitalization. Hospital
treatment expenses will be covered for diseases like fever and other diseases.
Under the cash benefit for hospital treatment, the policyholder will
get ₹60,000 for a maximum of 30 days in the hospital. This
plan can be availed for 1 year at just ₹699. This
insurance is
for treatment in any government or private hospital in the country,
if the swiper card member already has
other insurance coverage.  Even if
they have group insurance, they
can still avail the Arogya Bima Yojana. Personal
accident insurance benefits can be availed by paying ₹699 for 1 year.
In case of death or temporary disability, a
payment of ₹1000000 will be made and ₹90000 will be made for training.
Along with the treatment of diseases covered under this plan, the cost of malaria treatment in the hospital is also
included at ₹75000. The insurance
plan also covers
the World Black Chor Japanese Encephalitis
Disease, but to avail the insurance benefit,
you need at least 48 hours of hospital
treatment. All members of Preeti Card between 18 and
65 years of age can avail this plan.
Cardholders can choose
any of the three or more
insurance covers as per their needs and can
get a good insurance cover for themselves. So
friends,
how did you like the information about ICICI Lombard Health Insurance Policy?
Do write in the comment box. If you
want a video, you can ask and don't
forget to do so. Thank you.